<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.52l.icu</id>
    <title>52l Gamer</title>
    <updated>2024-07-10T09:42:56.590Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.52l.icu"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://www.52l.icu/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>is your source for exclusive reviews, demos, updates and news on all your favorite  gaming franchises.</subtitle>
    <logo>https://www.52l.icu/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://www.52l.icu/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2024, 52l Gamer</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double Dragon is about to launch a new 3D game! It will be available on consoles and PC in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/j27r5f0A8/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/j27r5f0A8/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to the latest issue of Weekly Famitsu, Arc System Works announced that it will launch a new 3D Double Dragon game, which will be released in 2025. It will be available on PlayStation 5, Xbox, PlayStation 4, Xbox One and PC platforms.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071022723151.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　According to the magazine, the new game faithfully recreates the thrill of old-school side-scrolling action games, updated with modern controls and difficulty settings, and leveraging Arc System Works' fighting game development experience. Jimmy Lee, Billy Lee, Roper, Abobo and more will appear in stylish 3D.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071022723660.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Double Dragon was originally an original game launched by Technos Japan in 1987. There are currently four official works. In 2015, Ark Systems announced the acquisition of the disbanded Technos Japan and obtained the rights to the Double Dragon game IP. Some former Technos Japan employees also participated in the development of the game.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_202407102272367.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Previously, according to the trademark application of Arc System Works, the game company of Double Dragon, Arc System Works submitted an application to the United States Patent and Trademark Office in June this year to register a trademark for the name &quot;Double Dragon: Resurrection&quot;.</p>
<p><strong>Double Dragon Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000071">Double Dragon Ⅱ - Noriam #OpenBOR #Hack #Gameplay</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000072">Double Dragon Collection - Announcement Trailer - Nintendo Switch</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000073">Why Did Double Dragon Neon Cause Outrage !?</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[75% of the players who voted will not buy PS5 Pro for GTA6. The reason is very real]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/v-cLA0wcI/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/v-cLA0wcI/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, IGN launched a poll on its official website, asking players whether they would buy a PS5 Pro in order to play GTA6 at the highest settings . As of press time, two-thirds of the 22,000 voters clearly stated that they would not.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071042800872.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Players who said they would not buy it pointed out that the PS5 Pro is not attractive enough at present. The reasons include that the current original machine has sufficient performance, the current generation of game lineup is still not comprehensive enough, and the PS5 Pro will most likely face scalpers' snatching and reselling when it is first launched on the market, etc.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071042800493.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　It is worth mentioning that Digital Foundry's technical editor previously analyzed that it may be difficult to achieve 60FPS when playing &quot;GTA6&quot; with PS5 Pro. If the analysis is accurate, the appeal of PS5 Pro to &quot;GTA6&quot; players may decline further.</p>
<p><strong>PS5 Pro Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000066">Where Is PS5 Pro? - Next-Gen Console Watch</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000067">PS5 PRO: Everything Revealed! Here Are All the Leaks</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000068">Marvel's Spider-Man 2 (PS5) Huge DLC Update! PlayStation 2024 Showcase Coming &amp; PS5 Pro Edition</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000069">✅NEW [PS5 PRO] RELEASE DATE, PRICE, POTENTIAL SEPTEMBER REVEAL, Holiday Launch on the Horizon?</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000070">PLAYSTATION 5 - NEW PS5 PRO BIG GAMES SHOWOFF !? / SONY CONFIRMS MULTIPLE EVENTS NEWS FOR PS5! / H…</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The development of "Marvel Wolverine" is nearing completion, and many core developers have moved to CDPR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/w8r-jx-NV/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/w8r-jx-NV/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-10T01:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, the industry has high hopes for Marvel's Wolverine , a game carefully prepared by Insomniac Games, which is expected to debut in the next few years. So far, no official news has been released. But recently, it was discovered that several developers have left the project to develop new games. Perhaps this means that the development of Marvel's Wolverine is close to completion!<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071090448716.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Unexpectedly, Mary Kenney, the deputy narrative director of Marvel Wolverine, announced on a professional social networking platform that she has officially joined the CDPR team and will be responsible for the mission design, dialogue writing and storyline control of the subsequent content of Cyberpunk 2077. What's more interesting is that she is not the only developer who has recently left the Insomniac team. Art director Aaron H also followed suit and also chose to leave the team and join CDPR, further exacerbating the outside world's speculation about the development progress of Marvel Wolverine.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071090448657.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Although this series of high-level developers' movement may seem like a major adjustment to the project on the surface, a closer look may indicate that the development of Marvel's Wolverine has come to an end and reached a relatively mature stage. CDPR also hired Anna Megill, the chief screenwriter of Fable. There is no doubt that CDPR has gathered a group of talented developers for the sequel to Cyberpunk 2077.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/10/584_2024071090448494.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>Marvel Wolverine Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000062">Marvel's Wolverine [Insomniac Prototype] Part 2 PC Gameplay 1080p Max Settings (READ DESCRIPTION)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000063">Marvel's Wolverine - Official Gameplay Reveal | PS5 Games</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000064">INSOMNIAC Marvel's Wolverine 1st Look at Madripoor</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000065">Wolverine(2026) First Look | Satisfying Brutal Kill Moves</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The server of "Naraka  Bladepoint" failed and the player's game settlement screen crashed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/jtIMONkQ0/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/jtIMONkQ0/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The latest news on July 9th: This afternoon, a large number of players reported that &quot; Naraka Bladepoint &quot; had game disconnections. The official Weibo account of &quot;Naraka Bladepoint&quot; released an announcement that a sudden network failure occurred in the server room, causing network fluctuations. Some players may have network connection problems such as disconnection and no response in queues.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070962156701.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　NetEase 24 Studio said that the development team is currently working hard to repair the problem. &quot;We sincerely apologize for the inconvenience caused to you and thank you for your patience and support for Naraka Bladepoint.&quot;<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070962156430.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Some netizens said that the game &quot;Naraka Bladepoint&quot; prompted &quot;Server is under maintenance, please try again later.&quot;<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_202407096215688.webp" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　&quot;Naraka Bladepoint&quot; is a &quot;battle royale&quot; game under NetEase 24 Studio, which became a free game on July 14, 2023. According to the official Steam website, the peak number of online players of &quot;Naraka Bladepoint&quot; today was 297,000, and it has now dropped to 48,000 due to server maintenance.</p>
<p><strong>Naraka  Bladepoint Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000057">Season 13: Aeon Treasure Scroll Preview | NARAKA: BLADEPOINT</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000058">New Weapon: Fistblades Gameplay Showcase | NARAKA: BLADEPOINT</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000059">The Fistblades might be too good... [Naraka Bladepoint]</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000060">Naraka Bladepoint • Ranked Solo Gameplay • Xbox Series X• 4K</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000061">Kunio Okawara x NARAKA: BLADEPOINT Official Crossover</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Steam page of ColdRidge, a turn-based exploration game in the Western world, is now online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/dtWfBi-mB/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/dtWfBi-mB/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-09T09:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Developed by Frog Collective Studio, a new western-themed turn-based adventure game with meat-and-pigeon elements - &quot;Cold Ridge&quot; has been listed on the Steam page. This game does not currently support Chinese, and the planned release date is to be determined.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_202407095121070.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　The story of ColdRidge is set in a western frontier that has not been tamed by civilization. The game will immerse players in a turn-based exploration game of the mysterious western world. In this land shrouded by an ancient curse, players need to traverse the dark wilderness, solve numerous mysteries, find magical artifacts hidden in the world, and explore mysterious areas that are not even marked on the map. The plains of Coldridge seem peaceful and tranquil, but in fact, undercurrents are surging, and countless secrets are waiting for you to uncover one by one.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070951209823.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Every decision will be the key to the direction of the story. In the wilderness, there are not only coveted treasures, but also unknown secrets. Are you willing to step forward, accept this challenge, and uncover the mysteries behind the guild?<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070951210849.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>ColdRidge Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000056">Coldridge - Official Reveal Trailer</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta puzzle adventure game "OneShot" launches 10th anniversary spin-off]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/slPFBpaw0/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/slPFBpaw0/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-09T09:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In order to celebrate its 10th anniversary, the meta puzzle adventure game &quot;OneShot&quot; has launched a commemorative spin-off &quot;OneShot The Pancake Episode&quot;, which is now available for download on itch.io<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070940248499.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　In this game, players will experience a special cooking course with Niko in a &quot;no one dies&quot; coffee shop. The game also comes with a real pancake recipe, so you can recreate the taste of the game in real life.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070940248312.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070940249431.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070940248419.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>OneShot Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000051">PANCAKES! - OneShot Episode 4</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000052">OneShot: The Pancake Episode (Full Playthrough/Gameplay) - PANCAKES!</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000053">OneShot: The Pancake episode</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000054">OneShot: The Pancake Episode (Full Gameplay)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000055">How To Make Mama's Pancakes | OneShot: The Pancake Episode</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy XIV Xbox version encounters setbacks! Yoshida Naoki apologizes and promises quick fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/8SjsFMIr3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/8SjsFMIr3/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-09T08:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With the official launch of the expansion pack &quot;Golden Legacy&quot;, Final Fantasy XIV has reached the peak of online player numbers in its 10-year history. However, this glorious moment is accompanied by the troubles encountered by players of the Xbox version, especially the frequent long-term freezing problem when switching between versions, which has caused troubles for many players' gaming experience.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070934726912.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　In response to this issue, Final Fantasy 14's navigator, Mr. Naoki Yoshida, personally expressed his &quot;deep apologies&quot; for the inconvenience experienced by players, and promised that this technical obstacle has become the team's top priority for repair. He revealed that although he has worked closely with Microsoft to conduct a detailed investigation and work hard to fix it, given the complexity of the problem, it still takes &quot;more time to thoroughly investigate and verify the solution.&quot; Naoki Yoshida called on players to remain patient and believed that the team would go all out until an effective solution was found and implemented .<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070934726856.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　In order to make up for the inconvenience of players during this period, SE officials responded quickly and announced a series of compensation measures: all Xbox version of &quot;Final Fantasy 14&quot; full version players will get an additional 8 days of free game time from 10:30 pm on July 4 (Pacific Standard Time), and will be given additional service time as compensation. For non-Xbox platform players, as long as they own the corresponding platform's &quot;Final Fantasy 14&quot; full version game, they can also enjoy 2 days of free game time, a total of up to 10 days.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/09/584_2024070934726306.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>Final Fantasy XIV Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000046">FINAL FANTASY XIV - Board of Turalism</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000047">Summary of Final Fantasy XIV's Story Up To Dawntrail</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000048">How Good is FFXIV Dawntrail, So Far?</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000049">FFXIV Dawntrail The Story of the Viper Finale (FFXIV Lore)</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000050">FINAL FANTASY XIV: DAWNTRAIL Launch Trailer</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Information hints: The Witcher multiplayer will adopt a career-based game mode]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/vy9L1ylwW/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/vy9L1ylwW/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-08T12:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>According to a report by Tech4Gamers, CDPR hinted in a job posting for a senior combat designer for The Witcher multiplayer game Project Sirius that the game will adopt a career-based gameplay. The multiplayer game Project Sirius is one of several ongoing Witcher projects at CDPR, which is also currently developing a new Witcher game and a remastered version of the original Witcher.<br>
<img src="https://images.ali213.net/picfile/pic/2024/07/08/584_2024070874850736.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　&quot;Use techniques such as behavior trees, animated graphs, and blueprints to implement combat behaviors for each character type,&quot; CDPR wrote in the job posting. They point to the concept of &quot;character types,&quot; which means a category-based system similar to how other multiplayer games divide characters into different specific responsibilities.<br>
<img src="https://images.ali213.net/picfile/pic/2024/07/08/584_2024070874754873.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　In addition, the job posting also states that the developer's goal is to make combat fun, satisfying, and scalable from early to late stages of the game, and the person who gets this position will report directly to the chief gameplay designer.</p>
<p><strong>The Witcher Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000041">The Witcher 4 REVEAL NEWS...</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000042">WITCHER 3 NEW ENDING FOUND 9 YRS LATER, NEXT RESIDENT EVIL &amp; MORE</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000043">Tier List: The Witcher + Bioshock | Tiempo de Videojuegos</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000044">The Witcher 4 will make The Elder Scrolls 6 look like a free-to-play mobile game.. </a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000045">King Ceres Fauna will banned forever Gwent in the Witcher World | 『Hololive』</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another championship, and FMVP? Why is Faker still so fierce at the age of 28?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/JFg42XAev/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/JFg42XAev/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-08T11:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Early this morning, the &quot; League of Legends &quot; event of 　　the 2024 Saudi Arabia Esports World Cup officially came to an end. The T1 team defeated the TES team 3:1 to win the championship, and Faker won the FMVP.</p>
<p>If this was Faker who just debuted in 2013, we might think it was normal, but 10 years later, why is the 28-year-old Faker still able to stand firm in the e-sports field and become the &quot;evergreen&quot; of &quot;League of Legends&quot;?<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070840455755.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
We all know that most e-sports players are between 17 and 22 years old, which is scientifically considered to be the peak of intelligence and reaction. After this age, the level of each aspect begins to decline, so many e-sports players choose to retire at the age of 24.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070840454890.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Like other professional players, Faker joined the e-sports industry at the age of 17, but he reached the peak as soon as he debuted. In his first year with the SKT team (renamed T1 in 2019), he single-killed South Korea's No. 1 mid laner An Zhangmen and South Korea's passerby Wang Yuelun with his outstanding strength, and won the S3 World Championship that year. The name of the newcomer Faker gradually appeared in everyone's vision.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835629885.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　In the following years, Faker's STK team also overcame all difficulties and won the world championship in S5 and S6. Faker's reputation became more and more famous, so much so that for a long time Faker became a synonym, and almost all players were proud to kill Faker alone.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835629234.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　However, all this changed after the defeat in the S7 World Championship. Many players left the team, and SKT began to decline. Faker, who was getting older, became a substitute for a while. Words like &quot;Faker is old&quot; and &quot;Faker should retire&quot; appeared one after another. However, Faker did not give up and continued to march towards his fourth championship.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835628384.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　In the S13 World Championship, Faker broke the doubts of the players and proved with his actions that &quot;Lian Po is old, can he still fight?&quot; Faker led the new team members to the top again after 7 years, and T1 added another star on the uniform. This also made Faker an insurmountable mountain in the history of &quot;League of Legends&quot; e-sports.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835629167.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Looking back at Faker's life, he has fallen from the peak to the bottom, and then climbed back to the top. If this were put in a novel, it would definitely be a cool male protagonist plot. But Faker's success can never be summed up by the word &quot;talent&quot; alone.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835705179.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　For those who have won the S-League world championship, they can earn a lot of money just by live streaming. But with his love for League of Legends, Faker has been on the road of e-sports year after year. In order to make up for the gap caused by his age, Faker only has continuous training in his eyes.</p>
<p>Previously, a blogger had posted Faker's daily schedule, which showed that Faker's daily activities included: sleeping, eating, training, playing solo, free activities, and training outside of games. Among them, the game time took up 12 hours, and training and playing solo each took up 6 hours. To borrow Faker's words: I never stopped working hard, I never chose to give up, so I believe I can definitely get back to the top.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835631722.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　As for when Faker will retire, Faker has previously stated that he wants to continue staying with the T1 team, and emphasized that as a professional player, he has been working hard to learn and grow, and he will continue to seize this rare opportunity.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2024070835629394.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
　　Although Faker is in LCK, his professional attitude and professionalism are worth learning for our LPL professional players. I hope that one day the LPL region can have a benchmark figure like Faker, leading the region to greater glory and achievement.</p>
<p><strong>League of Legends Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000038">Aurora - A 200 Years Champion? Or Perfectly Designed? |League of Legends</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000039">T1 vs TES Highlights ALL GAMES | EWC 2024 Grand Final |</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000040">Quantum's Vex - Best of LoL Streams 2519</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Nightfall 2 Sys:Celes" DLC character "Uzuki" trailer announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.52l.icu/TznpwgJvY/</id>
        <link href="https://www.52l.icu/TznpwgJvY/">
        </link>
        <updated>2024-07-08T09:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Publisher Arc System Works and developer French-Bread released a new trailer for the first DLC character &quot;Uzuki&quot; for the fighting game &quot;Under Night Incarnation 2&quot;. The character was originally announced in January this year and is part of the character season pass content for &quot;Under Night Incarnation 2&quot;. It is expected to be launched in August, and a live trial of the character will also be available at EVO 2024.<br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_7836605a0043cc3ce1d0d224872e4582.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_7673fe44f7edaf184e335333fdd0997a.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_fa00b54d256dabb68dc3044c1d1a580a.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_2562d799d064f97ab95061729cbd1176.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_73998315fd041e9901a79ee9a666c98c.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"><br>
<img src="https://img2.ali213.net/picfile/News/2024/07/08/584_68ab5856d4c3ad40a79c98c76ef6b9dc.jpg" alt="" loading="lazy"></p>
<p><strong>Nightfall 2 Sys:Celes Video</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000035">Under Night In-Birth 2 Sys:Celes Uzuki Reveal Trailer</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000036">UZUKI REVEAL TRAILER - UNDER NIGHT IN-BIRTH 2 SysCeles</a></p>
<p><a href="https://shrinkme.vip/no00000037">Uzuki The Black Monger Trailer | Under Night In-Birth II [SYS:CELES]</a></p>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>